Good morning.
Making, huh?
This is Aya Shirahama.
I'm going to go.
Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
It's all right.
Well, you know, we'll take care of it.
So, that's the entrance,
I'm going to sit down at the entrance and take a picture of you singing.
And when you get a shot of them singing, you can see them coming, licking their chupa chups.
What flavor?
There are about three flavors.
I wonder what flavor they are.
I'm the Chupa Chups character today.
Oh, I understand.
I can lick a lot.
I got it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
You will have beautiful days.
Even when no one is around.
Kindness never fades properly.
I have you safely.
I want to be
BGM on stage
Yes, cut.
OK, the image is OK.
Thank you for the rain.
You don't like it?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yes, I do.
You don't like it?
I can't eat strawberries.
I can't have strawberries.
I can't have anything strawberry-flavored.
It was a clean hit. I was so surprised.
When I asked him what flavor it was.
I was looking forward to it, but I thought strawberry wouldn't come...
And then it came.
It was perfect, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
But I'm getting used to it.
I think I smiled a little.
What camera guy?
Ah, Tetsuya.
Yay! Yay!
I'll take it.
We're going to do a two-shot.
Let me just get an image of the two of you standing in front of the trailer house before I get my shot.
You can see that they're waiting for the two sisters to come over.
A little bit more of them playing with each other in the middle of the shot.
And then at the end, they're playing with each other a little bit more, like they're doing it again.
Let's take our eyes off the road here, shall we?
Thank you for your time.
Okay, I'm ready.
Okay, please.
Okay, let's see.
Aya, once you're here, it's OK.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to try to hold on to it.
I'm going to try to hold it here.
I tried to squat down and stuff.
Leaning a little bit on the bike...
It's a little bit like leaning on a bicycle.
Yes, sir.
Feel free to do anything you want.
I understand.
Thank you very much.
Please do it.
Looks ası üz
acknowledge no goroi
Ni here.
I'm here.
I wonder why you are here Pedo
I'm curious about a lot of things and I want to look at them.
I understand.
I don't see anything.
Oh, I see a camera.
challenging is on every timer
Today
I had it wrapped around me.
It's cute.
Really?
I've never seen it like this before, so I was surprised.
He also did my mail.
It's cute.
I like the color.
I did it.
I chose this pink color.
Next time
I still say to myself to work harder on every shot.
Was your facial expression okay?
It was great.
Really?
Thank you very much.
I think I'm going to sleep.
You mean, you look like you're about to fall asleep?
Next, we will be taking pictures of Mina-chan and Chi-chan,
I always find the seniors to be very helpful,
Please watch them a lot.
Bye bye.
Thank you very much.